c2coffer.com 2014-12-16

# Privacy Statement - www.c2coffer.com

This policy show how we use and protect your personal information. The security of your personal information is very important to us. We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We will only use it as we have described in our Privacy Policy. By using this Site, you consent to our Privacy Policy set out below.

**What personal information do we collect?**

Registration Information and transactional information: At the time you register to become a Registered User of the Site, you will be asked to complete a registration form which requires you provide information such as your name, address, contact/billing information and physical address.  
Also transactional information based on your activities on the sites, such as bidding, buying, selling, item and community discussions, We may collect.

Statistical Information: In addition, we gather aggregate statistical information about our Site and Users, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, pages viewed, the number of sessions, unique visitors and so forth. 

Cookies Information: When you visit C2Coffer, you will be assigned a "cookie" (a small text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit this Site so we can enhance and customize your online purchase experience.

**How we use your personal information?**

Information we collect on C2Coffer may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways:  
•    Deliver merchandise and services that you purchase online  
•    Register you as a member of C2Coffer  
•    Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement;   
•    Respond to your customer-service inquiries or requests  
•    Contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service

We use your Collected Information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site's content, layout and service specifically for you. But we don't sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes. We and our users do not tolerate spam.

**When and with whom can we share your personal information?**

When people visit our website, they may see your user name, rates, city, and your items for sale. After making an offer or buying happen, the buyer and seller can see each other’s email and postal address to complete the transactions.  
We reserve the right to disclose your Collected Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of C2Coffer.com, our Users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.

**Safe Purchase**

We want you to feel completely secure when ordering from C2Coffer. We use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which encrypts (or encodes) sensitive information before it is sent over the Internet. After you bought, the invoice bring you to (also return back to C2Coffer) paypal website to make payment under SSL technology, so your info will be protected safely on the way. And your real making payment action work on paypal website, paypal is a safest place for your paying. And your payment be paid straightly to seller paypal account,C2Coffer do not accept any buyer’s payment .all paying process is at paypal website, after you finish paying process, you can return to C2Coffer. Paypal is our only online payment method, recommend you choose paypal, that is safe to buyers.  
To other off-line payment methods, such as westernunion and moneygram, buyers need contact with the sellers personally, and you also do payment personally. We can not collect these payment info online to protect safe purchase. 

**_Pay attention_** : C2Coffer do not accept buyer’s payment by any method, all payment buyers pay straightly to sellers. C2Coffer support a place to buy and sell, and we also support paypal online payment method to help buyers make payment to sellers, but we do not accept purchase payment.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective on the date they are posted on the Site. Our posting the amended and restated Privacy Policy will make such new Privacy Policy immediately effective. 

**Modify or Delete Personal Information**

If you have an account at C2Coffer and you want to change, modify or delete any of your personal information, you can easily to do so. Log in with your username and password at any time, click personal info menu to change your personal information.
